<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">NonoPic Classic</string>
    <string name="title_activity_acerca_de">About</string>
    <string name="reanudar">Resume game</string>
    <string name="reanudar_detalle">A previous game has been found which has not been completed, do you wish to resume it?</string>
    <string name="acerca_de">
    <big><b>NonoPic</b></big>
    \n\n
    Developed by <b>Adrián Jiménez Galán</b> as a project of the CFGS Multiplatform Applications Development at IES Comercio.
    \n\n
    The creation of this software has been possible thanks to the <b>libGDX</b> framework (libgdx.badlogicgames.com), used under the <b>Apache License Version 2.0</b> to run the game.
    \n\n
    The following audio files have been used in this software:
    \n\n
    <i>Yamaha CS-30L - Velocity Click - A#4 (Velocity Click-70-85.aif)</i> from modularsamples under the <b>Creative Commons 0</b> license.
    \nfreesound.org/people/modularsamples/sounds/315423/
    \n\n
    <i>Click</i> from lebcraftlp under the <b>Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported</b> license.
    \nfreesound.org/people/lebcraftlp/sounds/192277/
    \n\n
    <i>Charm</i> from Scrampunk under the <b>Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported</b> license.
    \nfreesound.org/people/Scrampunk/sounds/344696/
    \n\n
    Music created by <b>Blue Dot Sessions</b> (www.sessions.blue), used under the <b>Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International</b> license.
    \n\nIncluded songs:\n
    \n\t- Tuck and Point
    \n\t- Town Market
    \n\t- Liptis
    \n\t- Tiny Putty
    \n\t- Rose Ornament
    \n\t- Polycoat
    \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_instrucciones">How to play</string>
    <string name="tutorial1">NonoPic is a puzzle game based on nonograms.\n\nThe objective is to reveal a picture by following the patterns of the numbers next to the columns and rows of the grid.</string>
    <string name="tutorial2">Each number indicates the number of consecutive ticked boxes in each row or column.\n\nFor example, a 5 above a column means that somewhere in that column there is a group of five ticked boxes with no spaces between them.</string>
    <string name="tutorial3">If there is more than one number for a row or column, it means that there are multiple groups of cells, separated by at least one blank cell.\n\nIn the image you can see a case where a 2 and a 7 appear for the same row.</string>
    <string name="tutorial4">You will have to use logic to work out which boxes to tick and which not to tick.\n\nDo not forget to mark with an X the boxes that you know cannot be ticked!</string>
    <string name="jugar">Play</string>
    <string name="tiempo">Time</string>

</resources>
